Guide to the Larry McMurtry Papers
University of Houston Libraries
- McMurtry's Writings
  - Novels
    - Moving On
      - Lovebreaking, Third draft: Book II, Chapter XIV-XV, Book III, Chapter I-VI (Box 9, Folder 8)
      - Lovebreaking, Third draft: Book III, Chapter VII-X, Epilogue (Box 9, Folder 9)
      - Lovebreaking: Chapter I version that appeared in Red Neck Review, Summer 1968 (Box 9, Folder 10)
      - The Country of the Horn: Outline of Book II (Box 9, Folder 11)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book I, Chapter 1-6 (Box 9, Folder 12)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book I, Chapter 7-10 (Box 9, Folder 13)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book I, Chapter 11-16 (Box 9, Folder 14)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book I, Chapter 17-20 (Box 9, Folder 15)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book II, Chapter 1-5 (Box 9, Folder 16)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book II, Chapter 6-11 (Box 9, Folder 17)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book II, Chapter 12-15 (Box 9, Folder 18)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book II, Chapter 16-20 (Box 9, Folder 19)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book III, Chapter 1-5 (Box 9, Folder 20)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book III, Chapter 6-11 (Box 9, Folder 21)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book III, Chapter 12-15 (Box 9, Folder 22)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book III, Chapter 16-20 (Box 9, Folder 23)
      - The Country of the Horn, Second draft: Book II, Chapter 12-21 (Box 9, Folder 24)
      - Chapter I-V (Box 10, Folder 1)
      - Chapter VI-X (Box 10, Folder 2)
      - Chapter XI-XV (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Chapter XVI-XX (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Additions to Books II & III (Box 10, Folder 5)
        Manuscript
      - Introduction; Introduction, revised (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Review (Box 10, Folder 7)
        Clipping
    - Somebody's Darling
      - First draft: Note (Box 10, Folder 8)
      - First draft: Book I, Chapter I-V (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - First draft: Book I, Chapter VI-VIII (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - First draft: Book I, Chapter IX-X (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - First draft: Book II, Chapter I-V (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - First draft: Book II, Chapter VI-X (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - First draft: Book III, Chapter I-III (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - First draft: Book III, Chapter IV-VI (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - First draft: Book III, Chapter VII-IX (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - First draft: Book III, Chapter X (Box 10, Folder 17)
      - Second draft: Front matter; Book I, Chapter I-VI (Box 10, Folder 18)
      - Second draft: Book I, Chapter VII-XII (Box 10, Folder 19)
      - Second draft: Book II, Chapter I-VIII (Box 10, Folder 20)
      - Second draft: Book II, Chapter IX-X; Book III, Chapter I-II (Box 10, Folder 21)
      - Second draft: Book III, Chapter III-VI (Box 10, Folder 22)
      - Second draft: Book III, Chapter VII-XI (Box 10, Folder 23)
      - Second draft: Cuts (Box 10, Folder 24)
      - Second draft: Front matter; Book I, Chapter I-VI (Box 10, Folder 25)
      - Second draft: Book I, Chapter VII-XII (Box 10, Folder 26)
      - Second draft: Book II, Chapter I-VIII (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Second draft: Book II, Chapter IX-X (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Second draft: Book III, Chapter I-V (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Second draft: Book III, Chapter VI-XI (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Publisher's copy: Layout sheets (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Publisher's copy: Spine copy; Front matter; Book I, Chapter I-VI (Box 11, Folder 6)
        Photocopied copyedited transcript
      - Publisher's copy: Book I, Chapter VII-XII (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Publisher's copy: Book II, Chapter I-VIII (Box 11, Folder 8)
      - Publisher's copy: Book II, Chapter IX-X (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Publisher's copy: Book III, Chapter I-IV (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Publisher's copy: Book III, Chapter V-XI (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Introduction (Box 11, Folder 12)
        Transcript, with corrections; Photocopied transcript, with manuscript corrections
      - Advance uncorrected proofs (Box 11, Folder 13)
        Separation sheet
    - Texasville
      - Notes (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - First draft: Chapter 1-8 (Box 11, Folder 15)
      - First draft: Chapter 9-16 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - First draft: Chapter 17-23 (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - First draft: Chapter 24-30 (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - First draft: Chapter 31-40 (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - First draft: Chapter 41-47 (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - First draft: Chapter 48-56 (Box 11, Folder 21)
      - First draft: Chapter 57-65 (Box 11, Folder 22)
      - First draft: Chapter 66-74 (Box 11, Folder 23)
      - First draft: Chapter 75-82 (Box 11, Folder 24)
      - First draft: Chapter 83-90 (Box 11, Folder 25)
      - First draft: Chapter 91-94 (Box 11, Folder 26)
      - Incomplete first draft: Incomplete Chapter 81, Chapters 82-94 (Box 11, Folder 27)
        Photocopied typescript draft, with corrections
      - Incomplete second draft: Chapters 61-70 (Box 11, Folder 28)
      - Incomplete second draft: Chapters 71-81 (Box 11, Folder 29)
      - Incomplete second draft: Chapters 82-89 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Incomplete second draft: Chapters 90-98 (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Second draft: Chapters 1-10 (Box 12, Folder 3)
        Photocopied typescript draft
      - Second draft: Chapters 11-20 (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Second draft: Chapters 21-31 (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Second draft: Chapters 32-42 (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - Second draft: Chapters 43-51 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Second draft: Chapters 52-62 (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Second draft: Chapters 63-72 (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Second draft: Chapters 73-83 (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Second draft: Chapters 84-91 (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Second draft: Chapters 92-98 (Box 12, Folder 12)
      - Newspaper ad (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Undated draft page 974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Scripts
    - The Ballad of Mary Phagan
      - Background material: The Augusta Chronicle (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Background material: News articles (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Background material: Dinnerstein book (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - Background material: Chapter 7, Confessions of a Criminal Lawyer, Allan Henson (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Background material: Excerpt from Godlen's book; News article (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Background material: Article in The Tennessean, March 7, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Court records arranged by steps: Steps 29-37 (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Court records arranged by steps: Step 38 (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Court records arranged by steps: Steps 39-42, and unknown steps (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - Court records arranged by steps: Steps 43, 63-66 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Slaton Hearings arranged by steps: Steps 54-55, 57, 59, 62, 71 (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Background material: Unidentified photocopies (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - Notes (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Notes and step sheets (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Notes and doodle (Box 12, Folder 29)
      - Draft, May 1982 (Box 12, Folder 30)
      - Draft, July 1982 (Box 12, Folder 31)
      - Character list; Character notes, July 1982 (Box 12, Folder 32)
        Typescript; Photocopied typescript
      - July 1982 Step sheet (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - Note and typed letter George Stevens, Jr. to McMurtry; Typed letter Chris to McMurtry, with step sheet; Photocopy of all with typed note, July 1982 (Box 12, Folder 34)
        TLS; TL; Typescript; Photocopied typescript
      - July 1982 draft and revisions, with notes (Box 12, Folder 35)
        Photocopied typescript, with corrections and notes
      - Notes for last act, September 2, 1982 (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - Draft, September 1982 (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - Discarded pages (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - Draft, September 1982 (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - Draft, October 1982 (Box 12, Folder 40)
      - Draft, October 1982 (Box 12, Folder 41)
      - Notes (on envelope) (Box 12, Folder 42)
      - Draft, February 1983 (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Typed letter George Stevens, Jr. to McMurtry, with notes on draft copies; p. 307 of Harry Golden's book, February 1, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 2)
        TLS; Photocopied pages, with notes
      - Typed letter from George Stevens, Jr. to McMurtry, with notes on draft copies, February 3, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Typed letter from George Stevens, Jr. to McMurtry, with notes on draft copies, February 14, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Draft, February 1983 (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Second (?) draft (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - George Stevens, Jr.'s notes on second draft; Copies of book and draft pages with notes, April 19, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Second draft (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Second draft (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Production draft: Part One, March 1987 (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Production draft: Part One, alternate endings, March 1987 (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - Production draft: Part Two, March 1987 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Cadillac Jack
      - Screenplay by Tracy Keenan based on McMurtry novel (Box 13, Folder 13)
        Photcopied typescript
      - Description of movie version (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Cantrell
      - Background material: Gunning for Justice (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Background material: The Gunfighter Rides Again magazine article (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Background material: Court records, Opening statement, Counsel for the defendant (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Background material: Court records, Opening statement, Counsel for the State (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Background material: Court records, volume I (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Background material: Court records, volume II (Box 13, Folder 20)
      - Background material: Court records, volume III (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Background material: Court records, volume IV (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Background material: Court records, volume V (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Background material: Court records, volume VI (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Background material: Court records, volume VII (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Background material: Court records, volume VIII (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Background material: Court records, Closing Arguments (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Typed letter Gerry Spence to McMurtry, August 9, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Step sheet, (August 1983?) (Box 14, Folder 4)
        Typescript, with corrections; Photocopied typescript, with corrections
      - Draft, August 1983 (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Draft, August 1983 (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Draft, September 1983 (Box 14, Folder 7)
      - Draft, October 1983 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Draft, October 1983 (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Draft, November 1983 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Draft, with notes, November 1983 (Box 14, Folder 11)
        Photocopied typescript, with notes and corrections
      - Typed letter, Gerry Spence to Martin Starger, December 4, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 12)
        Photocopied TLS
      - Typed letter, Gerry Spence to McMurtry, December 27, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Typed letter, John Scott Turner to Gerry Spence, December 23, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Draft, November 1983 (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Draft: Notes, January 1984 (Box 14, Folder 16)
        Photocopied typescript, with corrections; Manuscript note
      - Draft, February 1984 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Draft, February 1984 (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - Typed letter, Gerry Spence to McMurtry, March 12, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 19)
        TLS
      - Draft: Typed letter McMurtry to Bob/Marty, July 1985 (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Draft, July 1985 (Box 14, Folder 21)
    - Crossing Niagara
      - Crossing Niagara, Alonso Alegr (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Crossing Niagara, Alonso Alegr (Box 14, Folder 23)
      - Excerpts from Alegr (Box 14, Folder 24)
      - Step sheet, October 22, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 25)
      - Treatment, October 1982 (Box 14, Folder 26)
      - First preliminary draft (Box 14, Folder 27)
      - First preliminary draft: Suggested corrections (Box 14, Folder 28)
        Typescript, with notes
      - Draft, November 12, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - Draft: Notes for revision, November 12, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 30)
        Mss notes
      - Draft: Pages revised out, November 12, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - Second draft, first version; Note (Box 14, Folder 32)
        Typescript, with corrections and notes; Manuscript note
      - Draft; Notes, January 2, 1983 (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - Draft, February 1983 (Box 14, Folder 34)
        Typescript, with corrections; Some photocopied pages
      - Draft, February 1983 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Draft; Notes, February 1983 (Box 15, Folder 2)
        Photocopied typescript; Manuscript notes on envelope
      - Draft, March 1983 (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Concept worksheets (Box 15, Folder 4)
        Photocopied drawings
      - Advertising mock-ups (Box 15, Folder 5)
        Layouts
      - Background information (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Background material: Newspaper ads and articles, 1859-1960 (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Background material: Newspaper articles, 1876, 1886, 1894, 1896-1897 (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Background material: Newspaper articles, various dates and undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Background material. Magazine clipping (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - Background material: "Stunts and Stunters" (Box 15, Folder 11)
      - Background material: Book excerpts (Box 15, Folder 12)
      - Background material: Illustrations from books (Box 15, Folder 13)
      - Background material: Farini news articles (Box 15, Folder 14)
      - Background material: News article and book excerpt (Box 15, Folder 15)
      - Photos of drawings of Niagara Falls (Box 15, Folder 16)
      - Photos and engravings of Niagara Falls (Box 15, Folder 17)
      - Background material: Bolles, The Beauty of America. (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Dance Me Outside
      - Dance Me Outside by W.P. Kinsella; Card with notes (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Research: Synopsis of Indian Films (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Typed and handwritten notes (Box 15, Folder 21)
      - Treatments (Box 15, Folder 22)
      - Draft, May 1985 (Box 15, Folder 23)
      - Draft; Notes, June 1, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 24)
        Photocopied typescript, with corrections; Manuscript notes
      - Typed letter McMurtry to Norman, September 27, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Draft, October 1985 (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - Typed letter McMurtry to Bonnie, 11/24/85, November 24, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Draft, November 1985 (Box 15, Folder 28)
    - Honky Tonk Sue
      - Background Material: The Legend of Honky Tonk Sue (Box 15, Folder 29)
        Bound typescript
      - Background material: The Colorado by David Sheridan (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Background Material: Honky Tonk Sue, First book (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - Background Material: Honky Tonk Sue, No. 2 (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - Background Material: Honky Tonk Sue, No. 3 (Box 15, Folder 33)
      - Typed letter McMurtry to Anthea, et. al., September 12, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 34)
        Photocopied TLS (2 copies)
      - Typed letter McMurtry to Goldie/Anthea, November 8, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 35)
      - Ideas (Box 15, Folder 36)
      - Notes (Box 15, Folder 37)
        Typed and manuscript notes
      - Possible scenes (Box 15, Folder 38)
        Typed and manuscript notes, some photocopied
      - List of characters (Box 15, Folder 39)
        Manuscript notes
      - A Treatment, September 1983 (Box 15, Folder 40)
      - Draft, December 1983 (Box 15, Folder 41)
      - Draft, December 1983 (Box 15, Folder 42)
      - Draft, February 1984 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Draft, February 1984 (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Typed letter to "Dear Folks", April 18, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Draft, April 1984 (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Draft, April 1984 (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - Draft with Tom Mankewicz's notes, April 1984 (Box 16, Folder 6)
        Photocopied typescript with corrections, with notes
      - Draft, April 1984 (Box 16, Folder 7)
      - Draft, April 1984 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Discarded pages (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Draft, June 1985 (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Draft, June 1985 (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Draft, March 1985 (Box 16, Folder 12)
      - Draft, October 1985 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Typed letter McMurtry to Peter with undated draft section (Box 16, Folder 14)
        TLS; Typescript, with corrections
      - Draft, June 1986 (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Draft, June 1986 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - HUD
      - Screenplay: Character and story notes (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - Screenplay (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - The Massacre at Fall Creek
      - Pendleton Area Sesquicentennial (Box 16, Folder 19)
        Photocopied publication
      - Draft, October 9, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Draft, October 9, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 21)
      - Typed letter Jack Clayton to McMurtry; Notes on rough draft (Box 16, Folder 22)
        TLS; Typescript, signed
      - Notes on rough draft by Jack Clayton (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - Notes on rough draft by Jack Clayton (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - Draft, November 1975 (Box 16, Folder 25)
      - Draft, November 1975 (Box 16, Folder 26)
      - Typed letter Jack Clayton to LM, with notes; Preliminary step sheet (Box 16, Folder 27)
        TLS, with notes; Typescript
      - Draft, December 30, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - Draft rewrites of pp. 49-52, 65, 102, December 30, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - Draft, December 30, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - Typed letter and signed note Jack Clayton to McMurtry, with typed notes with mss notes, December 30, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 31)
        TL; Typescript, with notes
      - Typed letter Jack Clayton to McMurtry with enclosures (Box 16, Folder 32)
        TLS, with typed and photocopied enclosures
      - Jack Clayton's personal suggested revisions, March 3, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 33)
      - New scenes (Box 16, Folder 34)
        Typescript with notes
    - Montana
      - Background material (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Background material (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Background material: American Indian Economic Development: (Box 17, Folder 3)
      - Background material: Field notes of Michael Wustner (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Background material: Northern Plains Resource Council: (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Background material: Northern Cheyenne Research Project (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - Background material: Corporations, the State and Energy Development in the Northern Rockies (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Background material: Study of impact of coal (Box 17, Folder 8)
      - Letter Michael Wustner to McMurtry, March 24, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 9)
        ALS
      - Background material: Native Americans and Energy Development (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Background material: A Social, Economic and Cultural Study of the Crow Reservation, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 11)
      - Background material: Lake Powell Research Project Bulletin, no: 57, September 1977 (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Background material: "The Waning of the West" by Stan Steiner: Natural History Special Supplement:, June 7, 1975 (Box 17, Folder 13)
      - Background material: Boyd Charter interview (with notes) (Box 17, Folder 14)
      - Background material: A Comparative Study of the Impact of Coal Development (Box 17, Folder 15)
      - Big Sky Blues by Steve Wax, Spring 1979 (Box 17, Folder 16)
      - Background material: Big Sky Blues; NEH application (Box 17, Folder 17)
      - Salty Dogs: Proposed titles; Synopsis; Opening sequence (Box 17, Folder 18)
      - Salty Dogs: Notes (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - Salty Dogs: Undated draft (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - Salty Dogs: Undated draft (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - Salty Dogs: Second draft (Box 17, Folder 22)
        Typescript with some photocopied pages, with corrections
      - Fate of the Bird: Notes (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - Fate of the Bird: Draft, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 24)
        Photocopied typescript; Cover
      - Kith and Kin: Draft, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 25)
      - Undated notes (Box 17, Folder 26)
      - Draft, June 1980 (Box 17, Folder 27)
      - Third draft (Box 17, Folder 28)
      - Draft, July 1980 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Draft, July 1980 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Raise the Titanic
      - Raise the Titanic, a novel by Clive Cussler (Box 18, Folder 1)
        This item has been removed from the collection. See separation sheet for details.
      - Screenplay by Eric Hughes (Box 18, Folder 2)
      - Screenplay by Eric Hughes (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Screenplay by Adam Kennedy (Box 18, Folder 4)
      - Screenplay by Arnold Schulman (Box 18, Folder 5)
      - Notes (Box 18, Folder 6)
      - Synopsis (Box 18, Folder 7)
      - TLS LM to Stanley; Synopsis (Box 18, Folder 8)
        Photocopied TLS; Photocopied typescript
      - Outline (Box 18, Folder 9)
      - Cast list (Box 18, Folder 10)
      - Rough first draft (Box 18, Folder 11)
      - Rough first draft (Box 18, Folder 12)
      - Draft, June 1, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 13)
        Typescript draft, with corrections and notes
      - Rewritten pages (Box 18, Folder 14)
      - Typed letter Peter M. Benedek to McMurtry, May 12, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 15)
      - Third (?) draft (Box 18, Folder 16)
        Typescript draft, with corrections; Incomplete
    - Riding the Cage/Indiana Moon
      - Riding the Cage: Draft by Zalman King and John Cougar, September 9, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 17)
      - Riding the Cage: Typed letter McMurtry to Lorie (Box 18, Folder 18)
        Photocopied TLS, with notes
      - Indiana Moon: Draft, December 1984 (Box 18, Folder 19)
      - Indiana Moon: Draft, December 1984 (Box 18, Folder 20)
      - Riding the Cage: Typed letter from WB, with mss notes, January 15, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 21)
        TL, with notes
      - Indiana Moon: Draft, January 1985 (Box 18, Folder 22)
      - Riding the Cage: Draft, July 1985 (Box 18, Folder 23)
      - Riding the Cage: Draft, July 1985 (Box 18, Folder 24)
      - Riding the Cage: Draft, January 1986 (Box 18, Folder 25)
      - Riding the Cage: Draft, January 1986 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - September, September (Memphis)
      - Cybill Shepherd's copy of September September by Shelby Foote (Box 19, Folder 1)
      - Draft, January 6, 1982 (Box 19, Folder 2)
      - Draft, March 1983 (Box 19, Folder 3)
      - Draft, March 1983 (Box 19, Folder 4)
      - Typed letter [Carlton] to Sybill [Cybill Shepherd], December 1983 (Box 19, Folder 5)
        TL
      - Draft, February 1984 (Box 19, Folder 6)
      - Draft, September 1984 (Box 19, Folder 7)
      - Draft discarded (?) pages, September 1984 (Box 19, Folder 8)
        Photocopied typescript pages, with corrections
      - Notes (Box 19, Folder 9)
      - Incomplete draft (Box 19, Folder 10)
        Photocopied typescript draft, with notes
    - Somebody's Darling
      - Character list and breakdown by scenes (Box 19, Folder 11)
      - Preliminary draft (Box 19, Folder 12)
      - Preliminary draft (Box 19, Folder 13)
      - Rewrite suggestions (Box 19, Folder 14)
      - First draft (Box 19, Folder 15)
      - Second draft (Box 19, Folder 16)
        Photocopied typescript draft, with corrections (2 copies)
      - Third draft (incomplete) (Box 19, Folder 17)
        Typescript draft (carbon)
      - Fourth draft I (Box 19, Folder 18)
        Photocopied and carbon typescript draft
      - Fourth draft I: list of changes and dropped pages (Box 19, Folder 19)
        Manuscript; Typescript pages (carbon)
      - Fourth draft II (Box 19, Folder 20)
        Typescript draft, with note
      - Fourth draft II (Box 19, Folder 21)
      - Fifth draft: dropped pages (Box 19, Folder 22)